ugiftideas.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - uGiftIdeas.com

* * *

Thank you for using uGiftIdeas.com. We wrote this privacy policy ("Policy") to help you understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices you have. The Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Policy by posting the updated version on this Website. It is your responsibility to check this Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the uGifIdeas.com service following the posting of any changes to this Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes. If the changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice or get your consent, as required by law.

Way Ventures, LLC d/b/a uGiftIdeas.com ("uGiftIdeas.com", "uGiftIdeas", "Company", "We", "Us" or "Our") knows that our users ("you," "your", "visitors", "user") care about how your personal data is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously.

Please read this Policy carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information. The information we collect ("Personal Data") may be "personally identifiable" (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or "non-personally identifiable" (meaning it can't be used to specifically identify you). We use both types of information and combinations of both types as described below.

We will not share your Personal Data with anyone except as described in this Policy. By visiting or using the uGiftIdeas.com website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or any other services we offer from time to time (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your Personal Data as described in this Policy. 

Information Collection

The information we gather from you enables us to personalize and improve our services. Our goal is to provide you an efficient and customized experience when using our Website.

Collection of Personal Data

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * information (such as your name, email and postal address, telephone number, sex, and country of residence) that you provide by completing forms on the Website, including if you register as a user of the uGiftideas.com service, subscribe to our newsletter, upload or submit any material through the Site, or request any information;
  * your log-in and password details in connection with the account sign-in process;
  * details of any requests or transactions made by you through the uGiftIdeas.com service;
  * communications you send to us, for example to report a problem or to submit queries, concerns, or comments regarding the Service or its content;
  * information that you post to the Site in the form of comments or contributions to discussions; and
  * IP addresses.

Uses of Your Personal Data

We will use the Personal Data you provide to:

  * identify you when you sign-in to your account;
  * enable us to provide you with the uGiftIdeas.com services;
  * send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us;
  * present products to you when you use the uGiftIdeas.com service which we believe will be of interest based on your geographic location and previous use of the uGiftIdeas.com services;
  * administer your account with us;
  * enable us to contact you regarding any question you submit through the uGiftIdeas.com service;
  * analyze the use of the uGiftIdeas.com service and the people visiting to improve our content and Services; and
  * use for other purposes that we may disclose to you when we request your information.

We collect information from you in a variety of ways, including through user registration, surveys, sweepstakes, reminder services, and other instances where you are invited to participate and volunteer such information.

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information, and the page you requested. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your computer through your browser that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We may also record the referring page that linked you to us; the page you visit after our site; the ads you see; the ads you click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral site; and other usage activity and data logged by our servers. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser to prevent or limit your computer's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of uGiftIdeas.com's best features. Our advertising partners and merchants may also transmit cookies to your computer, when you click on ads or product listings that appear on our site. This Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or merchants.

While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website. In addition, uGiftIdeas.com may collect information that includes website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the Internet. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Personal Data collected automatically.

When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Website), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Website, so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners, so that they can understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

In addition, any Personal Data, saved gift ideas or gift lists, pictures or image content that you voluntarily disclose online will become publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

Information Usage

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Data to anyone. We share your Personal Data only as described below.

**Advertisers:** We may share your Personal Data with our trusted affiliates and advertisers ("Advertisers") to display targeted advertisements and/or promotional offers and you agree that we may provide any of the information we have collected from you to an Advertiser. We may deliver a file to you through the Website (known as a "web beacon") from an ad network. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

**Merchants:** We may share your Personal Data with the merchants that list their products on our Website. We may deliver a cookie to you through the merchant website to track your actions on a merchant website. The merchants can also view, edit, or set their own cookies, when you visit their website by clicking a product link from our Website.

**Public sharing of your information:** Unless you have indicated in your Profile to the contrary, we allow the public and other members of the site to browse your saved gift ideas, saved gift lists. All comments, questions, answers, and profile information including your username, full name, and picture that you post on uGiftIdeas.com will be publicly available. Any content (including without limitation images and comments) you voluntarily disclose will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others, and may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels. Additionally, if you sign into the Website through a third party social networking site or service, your list of "friends" from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Website, and such "friends," if they are also registered users of the Website, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your Website user profile. We do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service.

User profiles

Unless You indicate to the contrary, user profile information, including without limitation your name, email address, and other information ("User Submissions") may be displayed to other users if you chose to enter such information on your user profile. Again, any content (including without limitation images, captions, and comments) you voluntarily post on the Website becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others, and may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels. Additionally, if you sign into the Website through a third party social networking site or service, your list of "friends" from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Website, and such "friends," if they are also registered users of the Website, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your Website user profile. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service.

Email communication

We may use your email to send information about related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions from uGiftIdeas or our Advertisers or our merchant partners. You may also receive notification e-mails from uGiftIdeas, which inform you of actions (e.g. forgotten password) that have been performed on the site.

Information Disclosure

We do not sell or rent any of your personally identifying data to third parties. Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Data may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. We may share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners, advertisers or others. For example, we may tell an advertiser and merchant partners on uGiftIdeas.com how many people or the percentage of people who click on a gift after viewing it.

We utilize certain features of Google Analytics Advertising that include: Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Google Analytics Demographics, and Interest Reporting Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. These features assist us in understanding our users and preferences. We understand that certain website visitors may not want their data to be used by Google Analytics and therefore, the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on is available. To opt-out of Analytics for the web, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and install the add-on for your browser. For more details on installing and uninstalling the add-on, please see the relevant help resources for your specific browser.

Legal Disclosure

If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights or property of the public, any person or uGiftIdeas.com; or to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

Business Transfer

We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy.

Third-party Advertisers

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on uGiftIdeas.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on uGiftIdeas. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Storage and Processing

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third-party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-in protections via that third-party site or service. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Data by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-in mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Data we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. In the event that we believe that the security of your Personal Data in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we will endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, we may do so by email. The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read that site's privacy policy.

Children under 18 Years of Age

You must be 18 years and older to register to use the uGiftIdeas website. As a result, uGiftIdeas does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that we have collected information from a minor under the age of 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

Email Opt-Out

If you do not want to receive e-mails from uGiftIdeas.com, please unsubscribe by clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of any of our e-mails. Alternatively, you can send an email to support@ugiftideas.com with the word 'Unsubscribe' in the email subject. We will process your unsubscribe request as soon as possible. There may be promotional email campaigns in process and you may continue to receive emails from us for a few days. We require up to ten days to process your unsubscribe request. After this time, you will no longer receive marketing emails from uGiftIdeas.com. You may still receive emails regarding your transactions; for example, when you request to reset a lost or forgotten password.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and/or any part thereof, at any time, so please review it periodically. We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of uGiftIdeas.com or the Website after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification. You understand that the most recent version of this Policy will be located on the uGiftIdeas Web site under Privacy Policy.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit uGiftIdeas website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](http://www.ugiftideas.com/terms/).

Questions

Please contact us with any questions regarding our privacy policy by emailing us at support@uGiftIdeas.com.

Alternatively, you can reach us at:

uGiftIdeas.com

20 Trafalgar Sq. Ste 401

Nashua, NH 03063

Phone: (603)823-3300

© 2017 uGiftIdeas.com.
